Many people have asked me what my position is on abortion and abortion rights,
especially since I was proudly the person responsible for the ending of something that
all legal scholars, both sides, wanted and, in fact, demanded be ended.
Roe v. Wade. They wanted it ended.
It must be remembered that the Democrats are the radical ones on this position
because they support abortion up to and even beyond the ninth month.
The concept of having an abortion in the later months and even execution after birth,
and that's exactly what it is.
The baby is born, the baby is executed after birth, is unacceptable,
and almost everyone agrees with that.